

Vitalii Bondarchuk

lunior Front-end / & React.js Developer

• Kyiv, Ukraine

+38 096 266 90 70 (Telegram)

S vit.bondarchuk

@ vit.bondarchuk@gmail.com

inkedin.com/in/vitalii-bondarchuk/

SUMMARY

Front-end Developer with multitasking skills. Supportive and enthusiastic team player to streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues on the future team. I'm a friendly, positive, highly motivated person. Attentive to details. More than five years of working experience in IT as a UX/UI designer.

SKILLS

HTML5 **JavaScript** UX / UI CSS3 React.is Figma SCSS / Sass Redux Sketch NPM / Yarn Git / GitHub Photoshop Webpack AJAX Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Front-end & UI/UX 12/2018 – present time

- support sites: Front-end & UX/UI;
- create design: web/desktop/HMI;
- logos, brandbooks, banners.

Luxoft, IT-company

UI/UX & Graphic Designer 07/2015 - 11/2018

- support designs for Luxoft's products;
- presentations/banners/prints;
- making video tutorials for software.

FCB, Advertising Agency

DTP-Designer 03/2008 - 06/2015

- working with whole range of prints;
- color correction and profiling;
- 3D-molding, stereo-vario.

KP Media, Publishing Holding

Technical Designer 10/2004 - 03/2008

- scanning, retouching, collaging;
- color correction;
- prepress.

GITHUB & DESIGN PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/vitbon

Be https://www.behance.net/vitbon

LANGUAGES







EDUCATION

Cursor Education

Advanced Front-end Course 07/2020 - 10/2020

• HTML5 / CSS3:

- JavaScript (ES5 / ES6+);
- React.js.

Vinnitsa Technical University

Faculty of Computer Systems 09/1996 - 06/2001

• C, Basic, Assembler coding;

- programming measuring devices;
- honors degree.

Kyiv Evangel University

Faculty of Christian Education 09/2014 - 08/2018

• branch of Global University (USA);

- modern western programm;
- American lecturers.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cursor Education

Advanced Front-end

07/2020 - 10/2020

• modern technologies; many practical tasks;

• excellent final result.

Luxoft

English Courses

- British programm;
- upper intermediate level;
- 10/2016 10/2018 • native speaker.

INTERESTS









POST SCRIPTUM

Does your company need a proactive specialist with a desire to develop and move your business forward? Contact me, I'm that person! ©

Design Photo/Video

Literature

History